

MARY MAYUMI FAVOR

CONTACT

Address

Brgy. Aquino, Bulan, Sorsogon

C. Phone

+639-56702-8215 +639-10385-8957

Web

fmarymayumi@gmail.com mayumsfavor@gmail.com

SKILLS

Communication

Organization

Leadership

Teamplayer

INTERESTS

Reading

Traveling

Designing

ABOUT ME

I am Mary Mayumi E. Favor, 21 years old, a residence of Barangay Aquino, Bulan, Sorsogon. A hardworking student new for seeking employment to help lessen the financial burdens during my tertiary years. I am an entry-level professional, enrolled at Sorsogon State University-Bulan Campus taking up Bachelor of Science in Information Technology. Passionate in providing services with the skills and capabilities I am good at. I believe in my fast learning abilities, commitment to succeed, and my relevant research made me fit for this position. I am totally aware of the importance of knowing the task I am applying for and the needed work ethics. I was awarded based on my personality to perform in my recent and current consecutive class, which I know, I will also be willing to expertly perform my proficiencies and strengths, and to also gain experience from this work field.

EDUCATION

Bulan North Central School-A / 2008 - 2014

Bulan National High School / 2014 - 2020

Sorsogon State University / 2014 - 2020

EXPERIENCES

St. John Paul II Parish

/ 2021 - PRESENT

Parish Secretary

Year 2021, I started to worked in St. John Paul II Parish as a Parish Secretary, because of this work I am able to help my parents even in a small way. I buy the things that I want.

ACHIEVEMENT

St. John Paul II Parish

/ 2019 - 2024

Parish Secretary

Year 2019, a unforgettable year which I passed the examination, because of this i learned that always do the best you can because what's meant for you, will come to you.

MY CODING SKILLS

HTML	
CSS	
JAVASCRIPT	
BOOTSTRAP	